A Guide to the Correspondence of the Poe Memorial Association, 1899-1911
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Correspondence of the Poe Memorial Association 1899-1911
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
38-406
Ca. 205 items (1 box).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Scope and Content
The papers consist chiefly of letters to Charles William Kent from literary notables and other dignitaries invited to an unveiling of the Zolnay bust of Edgar Allan Poe in the University of Virginia Rotunda on October 7, 1899. Miscellaneous papers include clippings about Poe, an account for the event, and a poem "At Poe's grave" by William Winter, read by Sara Sigourney Rice.
Arrangement
The letters are arranged alphabetically by correspondent's last name, and chronologically within each correspondent for those with more than one letter.
Contents List
- Charles W. Kent, notes, etc. re Poe unveiling [ca. 1899]
- Reminiscences of Edgar Allan Poe, clipping 1899
- Abbott, Mr. to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent 1899 September 20
- Abbott, W.R. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 2
- Abbott, Edward to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 26
- Abbot, Edward to Charles W. Kent 1899 November 8
- Aldrich, Thomas Bailey to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 30
- Allen, Edward A. to to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 25
- Allen, Wm. H. to to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 16
- Allmond, Marcus Blakey to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 3
- [Ammen, S.Z.] to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 3
- Anderson, Archer to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 16
- Austin, Alfred to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 17
- Bancroft, Frederic to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 24
- Bangs, John Kendrick to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 20
- Barbe, Waitman to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 4
- Bates, Arlo to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 20
- Baylor, Frances C. (Mrs. George Barnum) to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 30
- Benton, Joel to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 26
- Beirbower, Austin to President of University of Virginia [Poe Memorial Association] 1899 October 3
- Bigelow, John to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 19
- Blair, Maria to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association [1899] September 25
- Blair, Maria to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association [1899] September 29
- Bleyer, Dr. J. Mount to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent 1899 October 3
- Bonner, M. Lee to Charles W. Kent 1899 November 17
- Brent, Frank P. to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 2
- Brock, R.A. to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 3
- Browne, F.F. to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 16
- Browne, W. Hand to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Associatio 1899 September 19
- Bruce, Wallace to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 3
- Bruce, W. Cabell to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 19
- Bryan, J.P. Kennedy to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 28
- Burroughs, John to [Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association] 1899 September 28
- Burton, Richard to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 18
- Butler, Nicholas Murray to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 19
- Calisch, Edward to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 20
- Carman, Bliss to Charles W. Kent [1899 ante October 7]
- Carpenter, G.R. to [Charles W. Kent] [1899] September 16
- Cawein, Madison J. to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 18, 21
- Chandler, A.B. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 19
- Churchill, Winston to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 1
- Clark, W.A., Jr. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 Jul 7
- Coleman, Mary M. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 6
- Cowardin, C. O'Brien to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 18
- Currell, W.S. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association [1899] September 19
- Crane, Stephen to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 14
- Curry, Jabez Lamar Monroe to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 21
- Dabney, Charles W. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 22
- Daniel, Jon W. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 20
- Davidson, James Wood to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 17
- Davis, M.E.M. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 28
- Davis, T.E. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 23
- Dehron, J.C. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 30
- De Kay, Charles to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 19
- Didier, Eugene L. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 19
- Didier, Eugene L. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 1
- Didier, Eugene L. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 18
- Downing, Andrew to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 19
- Dreher, Julius D. to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 20
- Due, Isabel to Wm. M. Thornton [1899?] Jan 26
- Dugdale, Jennie Bard to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association [1899] September 23
- Duncan, George S. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 18
- Dunlop, George to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1900 September 1
- Dunlop, George to Charles W. Kent 1900 Mar 7
- Durrett, R.T. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 4
- Dwight, Timothy to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent [1899] September 24
- The Editor of "East & West" to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent 1899 September 22
- Edwards, Harry Stillwell to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent 1899 October 4
- Elam, W.C. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Assocation 1899 September 20
- Ellis, Powhatan to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Assocation 1899 September 24
- Emmet, Thos. Addis to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Assocation 1899 September 20
- Ennis, C.C. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1901 Feb 8
- Everett, C.C. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 26
- Fawcett, Edgar to Charles W. Kent [1899] September 28
- Fields, Annie (Adams) to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 17
- Flash, H.L. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 26
- Fletcher, W.I. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 21
- Ford, Paul to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent [1899] September 20
- Fortier, Alcée to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 20
- Frazer, Robert to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 23
- Frazer, Robert to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 7
- French, Alice to to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 28
- Garland, Hamlin to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 19
- Gates, Merrill E. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 4
- Gilder, R.W. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 25
- Gilder, J.B. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 24
- Gill, W. Fearing to Charles W. Kent 1899 Jun 14
- Gill, W. Fearing to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association [1899] September 27
- Gill, W. Fearing to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 28
- Gill, W. Fearing to Charles W. Kent [ante 1899 October 7]
- The Gilliams Press Syndicate to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 21
- Gilman, D.C. to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 3
- Glasgow, Ellen to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 22
- Gordon, Armistead C. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 19
- Gordon, Armistead C. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 19
- Gordon, James Lindsay to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 18
- Goucher, John to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 21
- Grant, Robert to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent [1899] September 29
- Guiney, Louise Imogen to Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 19
- Gunter, Archibald C. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 19
- Hadley, Arthur T. to [Charles W. Kent] [1899 Ante October 7]
- Hale, Edward E. to Poe Memorial Association [1899 ante October 7]
- Hardy, Arthur S. to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 10
- Harlan, Mr. Justice to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 20
- Harper, Wm. R. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 20
- Harris, W.T. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 16
- Harrison, Belle R. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association [1899 October 7]
- Harrison, Gabriel to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 17
- Harrison, Gabriel to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 25
- Harrison, Gabriel to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 27
- Hay, John to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 20
- Hayne, William H. to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent 1899 October 3
- Henneman, John Bell to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 21
- Herrick, Mrs. L.B. to Poe Memorial Association [1899] September 18
- Higginson, Thomas Wentworth to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 6
- Hoopes, Mary Howard (Peterson), [Maud Howard Peterson, pseud.] to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association [1899 ante October 7]
- Hopkins, Fred M. to Paul D. Barringer 1899 October 21
- Hosmer, James K. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 20
- Hudnall, R.H. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 25
- Hunt, T.W. [L.W. Hunt?] to to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 16
- Hutton, Laurence to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent 1899 September 25
- Jesse, R.H. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 19
- Jewett, Sarah Orne to [Charles W. Kent] 1899 September 19
- Johnston, R.U. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 20
- Johnston, Miss Mary to Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 25
- Joyce, John A. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 7
- Kennan, George to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 21
- Kerr, Andrew S. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 6
- King, General [Charles] to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent 1899 September 18
- Kinney, Coates to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 27
- Kirk, Ellen O. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 20
- Lanier, Clifford A. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 5
- Lee, Susan P. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 21
- Lefevre, J.A. to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 23
- Link, S[amuel] A[lbert] to to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 3
- Lobeman, L.H. to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 5
- Lounsbury, Thomas Raynes Ford to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 16
- Loveman, Robert to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 10
- Low, [Seth] to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent [1899 ante October 7]
- Mabie, Hamilton to to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 Jun 15
- Mabie, Hamilton W. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 28
- Mabie, Hamilton W. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 5
- Mabie, Hamilton W. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 3
- Mabie, Hamilton W. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 10
- McCabe, W. Gordon to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 22
- McClure, A.K. to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 23
- Manly, Louise to to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 23
- Mann, Carl to Charles W. Kent [1899 ante October 7]
- Marr, Mrs. Jancy Hope to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 3
- Mayo, A.D. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 12
- Mead, Edward C. to Charles W. Kent [1899 ante October 7]
- Mead, Edwin D. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 27
- Merrill, Austin H. to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 22
- Milburn, W.H. to to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 28
- Miller, Joaquin to Charles W. Kent [1899 ante October 7]
- Miller, Polk to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 6
- Mims, Edwin to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 2
- Minor, B.B. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 2
- Mitchell, Donald to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 8
- Moellenhoff, Johnanna to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1900 Feb 21
- Moellenhoff, Johanna to Charles W. Kent 1900 Mar 7
- Moore, Chas. Leonard to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association [1899 ante October 7]
- Moore, J.B. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 18
- Moran, W.H.W. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 7
- Moran, W.H.W. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 20
- Morgan, Appleton to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 24
- Murfree, Mary N. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 20
- Murray, K.F. to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 18
- Norton, Professor to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent 1899 September 21
- Orrick, Jesse Lewis to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent [1899 ante October 7]
- Page, Rosewell to to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 6
- Pancoast, Henry L. to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 26
- Pattee, Fred Lewis to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 24
- Payne, Wm. M to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 23
- Peck, Geo. R. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 19
- Penfield, Edward to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 22
- Perry, Bliss to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 3
- Perry, Bliss to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 16
- Piatt, Mr. and Mrs. John James 1899 October 4
- Pitter (?) to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 4
- Poe, Edgar Allan to Miss [Isabel] Duer [ca. 1899] Apr 24
- Poe, John Prentiss to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 2
- Pollard, Edw. B to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 21
- Powell, E.L. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 25
- Price, Thos. R to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 7
- Putnam, George Haven to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 22
- Putnam, Herbert to Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 23
- Reade, Willoughby to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 25
- Reese, Miss Lizette Woodworth to Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 27
- Reynolds, Le Chevalier [Elmer Robert] to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 14
- Reynolds, Le Chevalier [Elmer Robert] to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 16, 20
- Reynolds, Le Chevalier [Elmer Robert] to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 17
- Reynolds, Le Chevalier [Elmer Robert] to Charles W. Kent 1899 November 2
- Reynolds, Le Chevalier [Elmer Robert] to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 November 13
- Rice, Sara S. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 19
- Rice, Sara S. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 5
- Richardson, Mrs. Abby Sage to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association [1899 ante October 7]
- Richardson, Charles F. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association [1899] September 28
- Rolfe, W.J. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 20
- Ropes, John C. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 18
- Rossetti, W.M. to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 19
- Rowland, Kate Mason to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 2
- Sanborn, F.B. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 4
- Sartain, William to Charles W. Kent, Chair, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 17
- Sass, G.H. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 18
- Sass, G.H. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 3
- Saunders, Frederick to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 19
- Saunders, Frederick to Charles W. Kent, Chairman Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 23
- Schelling, Felix E. to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 27
- Scott, W.W. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association [1899] September 23
- Scott, W.W. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 25
- Scott, W.W. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 20
- Scollard, Clinton to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent 1899 September 18
- Scudder, Miss to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent 1899 September 22
- Scudder, Mr. [Horace Elisha, or Samuel Hubbard] to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent 1899 September 18
- Seawell, Molly Elliot to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 3
- The Secretary of the Navy to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 19
- Shaw, Albert to to Charles W. Kent, President Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 5
- Shepherd, Henry E. to Charles W. Kent, Chairman Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 18
- Sherman, Frank D. to Poe Memorial Association [1899 ante October 7]
- Shipp, Scott to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 19
- Smith, Edward J. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 Aug 2
- Smith, Edward J. to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 16
- Smith, E.J. to Charles W. Kent, Chairman Poe Memorial Association 1899 Dec 22
- Smyth, Albert H. to Charles W. Kent, Chairman Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 26
- Southwick, Henry L. to Charles W. Kent, Chairman Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 23
- Spofford, A.R. to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent 1899 September 19
- Stanard, Mary Newton to Charles W. Kent 1911 Jan 16
- Stanard, W.G. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 18
- Starr, Rev. Wm. E. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 22
- Stedman, Edmund Clarence to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 4
- Stedman, Edmund to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 10
- Stimson, F[rederic] J[esup] to Charles W. Kent
- Stockard, Henry Jerome to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 Jun 12
- Stockton, Frank R. to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 2
- Stoddow, Franicis H. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 27
- Swiggest, G.L. to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 1
- Taylor, Hannis to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 20
- Thayer, Wm. R. to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent 1899 September 19
- Thom, De Courcy to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 25
- Thruston, L.M. to Charles W. Kent 1899 November 29
- Toy, C.H. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 30
- Tracy, Marguerite to Charles W. Kent [ca. 1899?]
- Tracy, Marguerite to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 10, November 10
- Traylor, Robert Lee to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 2
- Trent, W.P. to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 19
- Trowbridge, John Townsend to [Charles W. Kent] 1899 October 5
- Trumbull, Sarah H. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 20
- Trumbull, S.H. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 30
- Trumbull, Sarah H. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 Dec 18
- Tucker, Beverley to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 6
- Turk, R.S. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association [1899 ante October 7]
- Turnbull, Mr. & Mrs. Lawrence to Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 30
- Tyler, L.G. to Dr. Barringer [Poe Memorial Association] 1899 October 6
- Tyler, Moses Coit to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent 1899 October 3
- Valentine, E.C.L. to [Charles W. Kent], Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 4
- Van Dyke, Henry to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 27
- Wallace, Lew[is] to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 25
- Ward, Mr. & Mrs. Herbert to Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 5
- Weightman, Richard C. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 30
- Wendell, Barrett to [Charles W. Kent], Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 24
- West, Charles E. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 [ante October 7]
- Whiting, Miss to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent 1899 September 29
- Williams, Jesse Lynch to Poe Memorial Association, Charles W. Kent 1899 September 28
- Wilmer, Richard H. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 19
- Wilson, James Grant to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 Jul 6
- Wilson, James Grant to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 October 5
- Wilson, Robert Burns to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September
- Wilson, Robert Burns to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association [1899 ante October 7]
- Wilson, Robert B. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association [1899 ante October 7]
- Wilson, Robert Burns to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association [1899 ante October 7]
- Wilson, Wm. L. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 25
- Wilson, Woodrow to Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 18
- Winchester, C.T. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 16
- Winter, William to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 Apr 4
- Winter, William to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 Jul 3
- Woodberry, F.C. to Charles W. Kent [1899 ante October 7]
- Woodberry, G.E. to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 5
- Woods, Katharine Pearson to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 16
- Woods, K.P. to Charles W. Kent [1899 ante October 6]
- Woodward, F.C. to Charles W. Kent, Poe Memorial Association 1899 September 18
- Wright, Marcus J. to Charles W. Kent 1899 September 19
- Wright, Marie (Robinson) to Charles W. Kent 1899 October 27